[{'section': 'Introduction', 'code': ' A.1', 'question': 'Has the company developed and published a Board Charter which is periodically reviewed and which sets out the Board responsibility for internal control?'}, {'section': 'Introduction', 'code': ' A.2', 'question': 'Do the Board Charter or company documents distinguish the responsibilities of the board from management in line with Code requirements?'}, {'section': 'Introduction', 'code': ' A.3', 'question': 'Is there a statement indicating the responsibility of Board members for the application of corporate governance policies and procedures of the company?'}, {'section': 'Introduction', 'code': ' A.4', 'question': 'How has the Board ensured all directors'}, {'section': 'Introduction', 'code': ' A.5', 'question': 'Do company documents indicate the role of the Board in developing and monitoring the company strategy?'}, {'section': 'Introduction', 'code': ' A.6', 'question': 'Does the company strategy promote sustainability of the company?'}, {'section': 'Introduction', 'code': ' A.7', 'question': 'Are all board committees governed by a written charter/terms of reference'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.1', 'question': 'Has the Board established a Nomination Committee comprised mainly of independent and non-executive Board members?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.2', 'question': 'Is the chairperson of the Nomination Committee an independent director?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.3', 'question': 'Has the board adopted and published procedures for nomination and appointment of new Board members?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.4', 'question': 'Is the Board size adequate for the exercise of the company business?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.5', 'question': 'Has the board adopted a policy to ensure the achievement of diversity  including age'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.6', 'question': 'Do the Board members represent a mix of skills'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.7', 'question': 'Has the board adopted and applied a policy limiting the number of board positions each Board member may hold at any one time?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.8', 'question': 'Have any Alternate Board members been appointed?  If so'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.9', 'question': 'Are independent directors at least one-third of the total number of Board members?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.10', 'question': 'Does the Board have policies and procedures to annually assess the independence of independent Board members?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.11', 'question': 'Do all independent Board members have a tenure of less than 9 years?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.12', 'question': 'Is the Board comprised of a majority of non-executive board members?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.13', 'question': 'How  does the Board ensure a smooth transition of Board members?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.14', 'question': 'Has the Board established an effective Audit Committee according to Code requirements?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.15', 'question': 'Are the functions of the Chairperson and the Chief Executive Officer exercised by different individuals?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.16', 'question': 'Is the Chairman of the Board a non-executive board member?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.17', 'question': 'Has the Board established procedures to allow its members access to relevant'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.18', 'question': 'Has the Board adopted a policy on managing conflict of interest?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.19', 'question': 'Has the Board adopted a policy on related party transactions to protect the interests of the company and all its shareholders and which meets the requirements of the Code?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.20', 'question': 'Has the company appointed a qualified and competent company secretary who is a member in good standing of ICPSK?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.21', 'question': 'Has the Board adopted policies and processes to ensure oversight of sustainability'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.22', 'question': 'Has the Board developed an annual work-plan to guide its activities?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.23', 'question': 'Has the Board determined'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.24', 'question': 'Has the Board established and applied a formal induction program for in-coming members?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.25', 'question': 'Do Board members participate in on-going corporate governance training to the extent of 12 hours per year?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.26', 'question': 'Has the Board set up an independent Remuneration Committee or assigned to another Board committee the responsibility for determination of remuneration of directors?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.27', 'question': 'Has the Board established and approved formal and transparent remuneration policies and procedures that attract and retain Board members?'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.28', 'question': 'How does the Board ensure compliance with all applicable laws'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.29', 'question': 'In the past year'}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.30', 'question': 'Has the Board subjected the company to an annual governance audit?'}, {'section': 'Rights of Shareholders', 'code': ' C.1', 'question': 'Does the governance framework recognize the need to equitably treat all shareholders'}, {'section': 'Rights of Shareholders', 'code': ' C.2', 'question': 'Other than at the AGM'}, {'section': 'Rights of Shareholders', 'code': ' C.3', 'question': 'How does the Board facilitate shareholders participation at the AGM?'}, {'section': 'Rights of Shareholders', 'code': ' C.4', 'question': 'Are minority and foreign shareholders holding the same class of shares treated equitably?'}, {'section': 'Rights of Shareholders', 'code': ' C.5', 'question': 'Is there evidence that the Board proactively provides information to shareholders and the media'}, {'section': 'Stakeholder Relations', 'code': ' D.1', 'question': 'Does the Board have a stakeholder-inclusive approach in its practice of corporate governance and which identifies its various stakeholders?'}, {'section': 'Stakeholder Relations', 'code': ' D.2', 'question': 'Has the Board developed policies'}, {'section': 'Stakeholder Relations', 'code': ' D.3', 'question': 'How does the Board take into account the interests of key stakeholder groups prior to making decisions?'}, {'section': 'Stakeholder Relations', 'code': ' D.4', 'question': 'How does the Board ensure effective communications with stakeholders?'}, {'section': 'Stakeholder Relations', 'code': ' D.5', 'question': 'Has the Board established a formal dispute resolution process to address internal and external disputes?'}, {'section': 'Ethics and Social Responsibility', 'code': ' E.1', 'question': 'Does the Board ensure that all deliberations'}, {'section': 'Ethics and Social Responsibility', 'code': ' E.2', 'question': 'Has the Board developed a Code of Ethics and Conduct (which includes sustainability) and has it worked to ensure its application by all directors'}, {'section': 'Ethics and Social Responsibility', 'code': ' E.3', 'question': 'How does the Board ensure that compliance with the Ethics Code and Conduct is integrated into company operations?'}, {'section': 'Ethics and Social Responsibility', 'code': ' E.4', 'question': 'Does the Board incorporate ethical and sustainability risks and opportunities in the risk management process?'}, {'section': 'Ethics and Social Responsibility', 'code': ' E.5', 'question': 'How is the company performance on ethics assessed'}, {'section': 'Ethics and Social Responsibility', 'code': ' E.6', 'question': 'Has the company established and implemented a whistle blowing policy?'}, {'section': 'Ethics and Social Responsibility', 'code': ' E.7', 'question': 'Has the Board/or management developed policies on corporate citizenship and sustainability and strategies for company use?'}, {'section': 'Ethics and Social Responsibility', 'code': ' E.8', 'question': 'Does the Board consider not only the financial performance but also the impact of the companyâ€™s operations on society and the environment?'}, {'section': 'Ethics and Social Responsibility', 'code': ' E.9', 'question': 'Does the Board monitor and report activities leading to good corporate citizenship and sustainability to demonstrate they are well coordinated?'}, {'section': '"Accountability', 'code': ' Risk Management and Internal Control"', 'question': 'F.1'}, {'section': '"Accountability', 'code': ' Risk Management and Internal Control"', 'question': 'F.2'}, {'section': '"Accountability', 'code': ' Risk Management and Internal Control"', 'question': 'F.3'}, {'section': '"Accountability', 'code': ' Risk Management and Internal Control"', 'question': 'F.4'}, {'section': '"Accountability', 'code': ' Risk Management and Internal Control"', 'question': 'F.5'}, {'section': '"Accountability', 'code': ' Risk Management and Internal Control"', 'question': 'F.6'}, {'section': '"Accountability', 'code': ' Risk Management and Internal Control"', 'question': 'F.7'}, {'section': '"Accountability', 'code': ' Risk Management and Internal Control"', 'question': 'F.8'}, {'section': '"Accountability', 'code': ' Risk Management and Internal Control"', 'question': 'F.9'}, {'section': '"Accountability', 'code': ' Risk Management and Internal Control"', 'question': 'F.10'}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.1', 'question': 'Does the company have policies and processes to ensure timely and balanced disclosure of all material information as required by all laws'}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.2', 'question': 'Does the Annual Report cover'}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.3', 'question': 'Does the Annual Report cover'}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.4', 'question': 'Does the Annual Report cover'}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.5', 'question': 'As a minimum'}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.6', 'question': 'Does the Board disclose the management discussion and analysis as required in 7.1.1?'}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.7', 'question': 'Has the Board provided disclosures as required in 7.1.1 on compliance with laws'}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.8', 'question': 'Has the Board made all required disclosures'}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.9', 'question': "Has the Board disclosed the company's risk management policy"}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.10', 'question': 'Has the Board disclosed information on shareholders'}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.11', 'question': 'Has the Board disclosed all related-party transactions?'}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.12', 'question': 'Does the Board include in its Annual Report a statement of policy on good governance and the status of the application of this Code?'}]
>>> exit()

13:53:21 in chitchat/chitchat-cli on î‚  main [âœ˜!?] via chitchat took 5m 0s
âžœ cd ..

13:53:23 in chitchat on î‚  main [âœ˜!?] via chitchat
âžœ python chitchat-cli/main.py
Indexing document...
  0%|                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                   | 0/78 [00:00<?, ?it/s]
Traceback (most recent call last):
  File "/Users/rqiu/Developer/chitchat/chitchat-cli/main.py", line 86, in <module>
    main(uploaded_file)
  File "/Users/rqiu/Developer/chitchat/chitchat-cli/main.py", line 39, in main
    sources = search_docs(index, query)
              ^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^
  File "/Users/rqiu/Developer/chitchat/chitchat-cli/utils.py", line 99, in search_docs
    docs = _index.similarity_search(query, k=5)
           ^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^
  File "/Users/rqiu/Developer/chitchat/.venv/lib/python3.11/site-packages/langchain/vectorstores/faiss.py", line 166, in similarity_search
    docs_and_scores = self.similarity_search_with_score(query, k)
                      ^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^
  File "/Users/rqiu/Developer/chitchat/.venv/lib/python3.11/site-packages/langchain/vectorstores/faiss.py", line 135, in similarity_search_with_score
    embedding = self.embedding_function(query)
                ^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^
  File "/Users/rqiu/Developer/chitchat/chitchat-cli/embeddings.py", line 119, in embed_query
    embedding = self._embedding_func(text, engine=self.query_model_name)
                ^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^
  File "/Users/rqiu/Developer/chitchat/.venv/lib/python3.11/site-packages/tenacity/__init__.py", line 326, in wrapped_f
    return self(f, *args, **kw)
           ^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^
  File "/Users/rqiu/Developer/chitchat/.venv/lib/python3.11/site-packages/tenacity/__init__.py", line 406, in __call__
    do = self.iter(retry_state=retry_state)
         ^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^
  File "/Users/rqiu/Developer/chitchat/.venv/lib/python3.11/site-packages/tenacity/__init__.py", line 351, in iter
    return fut.result()
           ^^^^^^^^^^^^
  File "/opt/homebrew/Cellar/python@3.11/3.11.2/Frameworks/Python.framework/Versions/3.11/lib/python3.11/concurrent/futures/_base.py", line 449, in result
    return self.__get_result()
           ^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^
  File "/opt/homebrew/Cellar/python@3.11/3.11.2/Frameworks/Python.framework/Versions/3.11/lib/python3.11/concurrent/futures/_base.py", line 401, in __get_result
    raise self._exception
  File "/Users/rqiu/Developer/chitchat/.venv/lib/python3.11/site-packages/tenacity/__init__.py", line 409, in __call__
    result = fn(*args, **kwargs)
             ^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^
  File "/Users/rqiu/Developer/chitchat/chitchat-cli/embeddings.py", line 92, in _embedding_func
    text = text.replace("\n", " ")
           ^^^^^^^^^^^^
AttributeError: 'dict' object has no attribute 'replace'

13:53:30 in chitchat on î‚  main [âœ˜!?] via chitchat took 4s
âžœ python chitchat-cli/main.py
Indexing document...
100%|â–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆâ–ˆ| 78/78 [05:26<00:00,  4.19s/it]
[{'section': 'Introduction', 'code': ' A.1', 'question': 'Has the company developed and published a Board Charter which is periodically reviewed and which sets out the Board responsibility for internal control?', 'answer': 'There is no information provided to answer the question. \n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Introduction', 'code': ' A.2', 'question': 'Do the Board Charter or company documents distinguish the responsibilities of the board from management in line with Code requirements?', 'answer': 'No information is provided about the Board Charter or company documents and their distinction between the responsibilities of the board and management in line with Code requirements.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Introduction', 'code': ' A.3', 'question': 'Is there a statement indicating the responsibility of Board members for the application of corporate governance policies and procedures of the company?', 'answer': 'No, there is no statement indicating the responsibility of Board members for the application of corporate governance policies and procedures of the company in the provided document excerpts.\n', 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.'], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-3', '1-1', '1-2']}, {'section': 'Introduction', 'code': ' A.4', 'question': 'How has the Board ensured all directors', 'answer': "The Board has ensured all directors by implementing eight Performance Standards that define environmental and social requirements for investment projects, including assessment and management of environmental and social risks and impacts, labor and working conditions, resource efficiency and pollution prevention, community health, safety, and security, land acquisition and involuntary resettlement, biodiversity conservation and sustainable management of living natural resources, cultural heritage, and indigenous peoples' rights. \n", 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.'], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-1', '1-2']}, {'section': 'Introduction', 'code': ' A.5', 'question': 'Do company documents indicate the role of the Board in developing and monitoring the company strategy?', 'answer': 'No, the provided company documents do not indicate the role of the Board in developing and monitoring the company strategy. \n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Introduction', 'code': ' A.6', 'question': 'Does the company strategy promote sustainability of the company?', 'answer': 'Yes, the company strategy promotes sustainability through its adoption of Performance Standards that aim to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, sustainable management of living natural resources, fair and safe working conditions, minimizing environmental footprint, ensuring community health and safety, fair treatment of affected communities during land acquisition and resettlement, identification and safeguarding of cultural heritage resources, and engagement with indigenous peoples in a culturally appropriate manner. \n', 'source_contents': ['Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.'], 'source_pages': ['1-2', '1-0', '1-1', '1-3']}, {'section': 'Introduction', 'code': ' A.7', 'question': 'Are all board committees governed by a written charter/terms of reference', 'answer': 'The document excerpts do not provide a clear answer to whether all board committees are governed by a written charter/terms of reference. \n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.1', 'question': 'Has the Board established a Nomination Committee comprised mainly of independent and non-executive Board members?', 'answer': 'There is no information provided to answer this question.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.2', 'question': 'Is the chairperson of the Nomination Committee an independent director?', 'answer': 'There is no information in the provided document excerpts to answer whether the chairperson of the Nomination Committee is an independent director.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.3', 'question': 'Has the board adopted and published procedures for nomination and appointment of new Board members?', 'answer': 'There is no information provided about whether or not the board has adopted and published procedures for nomination and appointment of new Board members.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.4', 'question': 'Is the Board size adequate for the exercise of the company business?', 'answer': 'There is no information provided in the document excerpts to answer this question.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.5', 'question': 'Has the board adopted a policy to ensure the achievement of diversity  including age', 'answer': 'There is no information provided in the document excerpts regarding whether the board has adopted a policy to ensure the achievement of diversity including age. \n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.6', 'question': 'Do the Board members represent a mix of skills', 'answer': 'Yes, the Board members represent a mix of skills, but the document excerpts do not provide specific information on the composition of the Board. \n', 'source_contents': ['Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration."], 'source_pages': ['1-3', '1-0', '1-2', '1-1']}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.7', 'question': 'Has the board adopted and applied a policy limiting the number of board positions each Board member may hold at any one time?', 'answer': 'No information provided in the document excerpts suggests whether the board has adopted and applied a policy limiting the number of board positions each Board member may hold at any one time.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.8', 'question': 'Have any Alternate Board members been appointed?  If so', 'answer': 'There is no information provided regarding the appointment of Alternate Board members.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.9', 'question': 'Are independent directors at least one-third of the total number of Board members?', 'answer': 'The given document excerpts do not provide information pertaining to whether independent directors are at least one-third of the total number of Board members. \n', 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.'], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-1', '1-2', '1-3']}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.10', 'question': 'Does the Board have policies and procedures to annually assess the independence of independent Board members?', 'answer': 'No information is provided about whether the Board has policies and procedures to annually assess the independence of independent Board members.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.11', 'question': 'Do all independent Board members have a tenure of less than 9 years?', 'answer': 'There is no information provided in the given document excerpts to answer this question. \n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.12', 'question': 'Is the Board comprised of a majority of non-executive board members?', 'answer': 'There is no information provided in the document excerpts that can answer the question of whether the Board is comprised of a majority of non-executive board members.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.13', 'question': 'How  does the Board ensure a smooth transition of Board members?', 'answer': 'There is no information provided in the document excerpts on how the Board ensures a smooth transition of Board members.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.14', 'question': 'Has the Board established an effective Audit Committee according to Code requirements?', 'answer': 'There is no information provided to answer the question about the establishment of an effective Audit Committee according to Code requirements.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.15', 'question': 'Are the functions of the Chairperson and the Chief Executive Officer exercised by different individuals?', 'answer': 'There is no information provided to answer this question.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.16', 'question': 'Is the Chairman of the Board a non-executive board member?', 'answer': 'There is no information provided in the document excerpts to answer this question. \n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.17', 'question': 'Has the Board established procedures to allow its members access to relevant', 'answer': "The document provides information on the International Finance Corporation's eight Performance Standards, including Performance Standards 1-8, which cover assessment and management of environmental and social risks and impacts, labor and working conditions, biodiversity conservation and sustainable management of living natural resources, indigenous peoples, resource efficiency and pollution prevention, community health, safety, and security, and land acquisition and involuntary resettlement. The document does not provide information on whether the Board has established procedures to allow its members access to relevant information.\n", 'source_contents': ['Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration."], 'source_pages': ['1-3', '1-0', '1-2', '1-1']}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.18', 'question': 'Has the Board adopted a policy on managing conflict of interest?', 'answer': 'It is unclear whether the Board has adopted a policy on managing conflict of interest, as none of the provided document excerpts mention it. \n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.19', 'question': 'Has the Board adopted a policy on related party transactions to protect the interests of the company and all its shareholders and which meets the requirements of the Code?', 'answer': 'The given document does not provide information on whether or not the Board has adopted a policy on related party transactions to protect the interests of the company and all its shareholders and which meets the requirements of the Code.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.20', 'question': 'Has the company appointed a qualified and competent company secretary who is a member in good standing of ICPSK?', 'answer': 'There is no information provided in the document excerpts to determine whether or not the company appointed a qualified and competent company secretary who is a member in good standing of ICPSK.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.21', 'question': 'Has the Board adopted policies and processes to ensure oversight of sustainability', 'answer': "The Board has adopted policies and processes to ensure oversight of sustainability through the International Finance Corporation's eight Performance Standards, which include standards for biodiversity conservation, indigenous peoples, resource efficiency, pollution prevention, community health and safety, land acquisition and involuntary resettlement, assessment and management of environmental and social risks and impacts, labor and working conditions, and cultural heritage. \n", 'source_contents': ['Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.'], 'source_pages': ['1-2', '1-1', '1-0', '1-3']}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.22', 'question': 'Has the Board developed an annual work-plan to guide its activities?', 'answer': 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC) has developed eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects, including standards for cultural heritage, resource efficiency and pollution prevention, community health, safety, and security, land acquisition and involuntary resettlement, biodiversity conservation and sustainable management of living natural resources, and indigenous peoples. However, there is no reference to the Board developing an annual work-plan to guide its activities in the provided document excerpts.\n', 'source_contents': ['Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.'], 'source_pages': ['1-3', '1-1', '1-2', '1-0']}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.23', 'question': 'Has the Board determined', 'answer': 'The provided document excerpts do not answer the question of whether the Board has determined something. \n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.24', 'question': 'Has the Board established and applied a formal induction program for in-coming members?', 'answer': 'There is no information provided in the document excerpts regarding the establishment and application of a formal induction program for incoming members of a board. \n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.25', 'question': 'Do Board members participate in on-going corporate governance training to the extent of 12 hours per year?', 'answer': 'No information is provided about whether Board members participate in on-going corporate governance training to the extent of 12 hours per year.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.26', 'question': 'Has the Board set up an independent Remuneration Committee or assigned to another Board committee the responsibility for determination of remuneration of directors?', 'answer': 'There is no information provided in the document excerpts about whether the Board has set up an independent Remuneration Committee or assigned to another Board committee the responsibility for determination of remuneration of directors.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.27', 'question': 'Has the Board established and approved formal and transparent remuneration policies and procedures that attract and retain Board members?', 'answer': 'There is no information provided in the document excerpts regarding whether the Board has established and approved formal and transparent remuneration policies and procedures that attract and retain Board members.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.28', 'question': 'How does the Board ensure compliance with all applicable laws', 'answer': "The Board ensures compliance with all applicable laws through the International Finance Corporation's eight Performance Standards, which require clients to identify and assess potential environmental and social risks, ensure fair and safe working conditions, minimize environmental footprint, ensure community health and safety, provide fair treatment during land acquisition and resettlement, conserve biodiversity and natural resources, engage with indigenous peoples, and safeguard cultural heritage resources. \n", 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.'], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-1', '1-2', '1-3']}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.29', 'question': 'In the past year', 'answer': 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC) has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These standards include assessing and managing environmental and social risks and impacts, ensuring fair and safe working conditions, minimizing environmental footprint, ensuring community health and safety, fair treatment of affected communities during land acquisition and resettlement, biodiversity conservation, engaging with indigenous peoples, and identifying and safeguarding cultural heritage resources. \n', 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.'], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-1', '1-2']}, {'section': 'Board Operations and Control', 'code': ' B.30', 'question': 'Has the Board subjected the company to an annual governance audit?', 'answer': 'There is no information provided in the given document excerpts to answer whether or not the Board has subjected the company to an annual governance audit.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Rights of Shareholders', 'code': ' C.1', 'question': 'Does the governance framework recognize the need to equitably treat all shareholders', 'answer': "Yes, the governance framework recognizes the need to equitably treat all shareholders as evidenced by the International Finance Corporation's Performance Standards, which includes standards for fair working conditions, no discrimination, respect for indigenous peoples' rights, and fair treatment of affected communities during land acquisition and resettlement. \n", 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration."], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-2', '1-3', '1-1']}, {'section': 'Rights of Shareholders', 'code': ' C.2', 'question': 'Other than at the AGM', 'answer': 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC) has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects, including requirements for fair and safe working conditions, minimizing environmental footprint and maximizing resource efficiency, ensuring the safety and security of local communities and employees, fair treatment of affected communities during land acquisition and resettlement, identifying and safeguarding cultural heritage resources, conserving natural habitats and biodiversity, and recognizing the rights of indigenous peoples. \n', 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.'], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-1', '1-3', '1-2']}, {'section': 'Rights of Shareholders', 'code': ' C.3', 'question': 'How does the Board facilitate shareholders participation at the AGM?', 'answer': 'There is no information provided in the document excerpts regarding how the Board facilitates shareholders participation at the AGM.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Rights of Shareholders', 'code': ' C.4', 'question': 'Are minority and foreign shareholders holding the same class of shares treated equitably?', 'answer': 'The provided document excerpts do not provide information on whether minority and foreign shareholders holding the same class of shares are treated equitably. \n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Rights of Shareholders', 'code': ' C.5', 'question': 'Is there evidence that the Board proactively provides information to shareholders and the media', 'answer': 'No, there is no evidence in the provided document excerpts that the Board proactively provides information to shareholders and the media.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Stakeholder Relations', 'code': ' D.1', 'question': 'Does the Board have a stakeholder-inclusive approach in its practice of corporate governance and which identifies its various stakeholders?', 'answer': "The provided document excerpts do not provide a clear answer to whether the Board has a stakeholder-inclusive approach in its practice of corporate governance and which identifies its various stakeholders. The documents provide information on the International Finance Corporation's Performance Standards for environmental and social requirements for investment projects, which include requirements for engaging with affected communities and recognizing the rights of indigenous peoples, but it does not specifically mention the Board's approach to identifying stakeholders in its corporate governance practice. \n", 'source_contents': ['Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration."], 'source_pages': ['1-3', '1-0', '1-2', '1-1']}, {'section': 'Stakeholder Relations', 'code': ' D.2', 'question': 'Has the Board developed policies', 'answer': 'The Board has developed eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects, including assessment and management of environmental and social risks and impacts, labor and working conditions, resource efficiency and pollution prevention, community health, safety, and security, land acquisition and involuntary resettlement, biodiversity conservation and sustainable management of living natural resources, indigenous peoples, and cultural heritage. \n', 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.'], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-1', '1-3', '1-2']}, {'section': 'Stakeholder Relations', 'code': ' D.3', 'question': 'How does the Board take into account the interests of key stakeholder groups prior to making decisions?', 'answer': "The Board takes into account the interests of key stakeholder groups prior to making decisions through the adoption of Performance Standards that address environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards involve minimizing environmental impact, ensuring community health and safety, fair treatment of affected communities, safeguarding cultural heritage resources, assessing and managing environmental and social risks, fair and safe working conditions, biodiversity conservation, and recognition of indigenous peoples' rights. \n", 'source_contents': ["Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.'], 'source_pages': ['1-1', '1-3', '1-0', '1-2']}, {'section': 'Stakeholder Relations', 'code': ' D.4', 'question': 'How does the Board ensure effective communications with stakeholders?', 'answer': 'The Board ensures effective communications with stakeholders through the adoption of eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects, including engaging with affected communities, ensuring safety and security, and obtaining free, prior, and informed consent from indigenous peoples. These standards also require clients to identify and assess potential environmental and social risks and impacts, develop management plans to avoid or mitigate negative impacts, and establish fair and safe working conditions. \n', 'source_contents': ['Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.'], 'source_pages': ['1-3', '1-1', '1-2', '1-0']}, {'section': 'Stakeholder Relations', 'code': ' D.5', 'question': 'Has the Board established a formal dispute resolution process to address internal and external disputes?', 'answer': 'There is no information provided regarding whether or not the Board has established a formal dispute resolution process to address internal and external disputes.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Ethics and Social Responsibility', 'code': ' E.1', 'question': 'Does the Board ensure that all deliberations', 'answer': 'The provided document excerpts do not contain information about whether the Board ensures that all deliberations. \n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Ethics and Social Responsibility', 'code': ' E.2', 'question': 'Has the Board developed a Code of Ethics and Conduct (which includes sustainability) and has it worked to ensure its application by all directors', 'answer': 'The provided document excerpts do not provide information about whether the Board has developed a Code of Ethics and Conduct, nor whether it has worked to ensure its application by all directors. \n', 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.'], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-2', '1-1', '1-3']}, {'section': 'Ethics and Social Responsibility', 'code': ' E.3', 'question': 'How does the Board ensure that compliance with the Ethics Code and Conduct is integrated into company operations?', 'answer': 'It is unclear how the Board ensures that compliance with the Ethics Code and Conduct is integrated into company operations based on the provided document excerpts. \n', 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.'], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-1', '1-3', '1-2']}, {'section': 'Ethics and Social Responsibility', 'code': ' E.4', 'question': 'Does the Board incorporate ethical and sustainability risks and opportunities in the risk management process?', 'answer': "The document provides information on the International Finance Corporation's eight Performance Standards that define environmental and social requirements for investment projects, including the assessment and management of environmental and social risks and impacts, labor and working conditions, biodiversity conservation, indigenous peoples' rights, resource efficiency and pollution prevention, community health, safety, and security, land acquisition and involuntary resettlement, and cultural heritage. The document does not explicitly state whether the Board incorporates ethical and sustainability risks and opportunities in the risk management process, but the Performance Standards suggest a high level of consideration for ethical and sustainability concerns in investment projects. \n", 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.'], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-2', '1-1', '1-3']}, {'section': 'Ethics and Social Responsibility', 'code': ' E.5', 'question': 'How is the company performance on ethics assessed', 'answer': 'The company performance on ethics is assessed based on eight Performance Standards set by the International Finance Corporation (IFC), which define environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These include assessment and management of environmental and social risks and impacts, labor and working conditions, resource efficiency and pollution prevention, community health, safety, and security, land acquisition and involuntary resettlement, biodiversity conservation and sustainable management of living natural resources, indigenous peoples, and cultural heritage. \n', 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.'], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-1', '1-2']}, {'section': 'Ethics and Social Responsibility', 'code': ' E.6', 'question': 'Has the company established and implemented a whistle blowing policy?', 'answer': 'It is unclear whether or not the company has established and implemented a whistleblower policy as the provided document excerpts do not mention it. \n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Ethics and Social Responsibility', 'code': ' E.7', 'question': 'Has the Board/or management developed policies on corporate citizenship and sustainability and strategies for company use?', 'answer': 'It is unclear whether the Board or management of the company in question has developed policies on corporate citizenship and sustainability and strategies for company use. However, the International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects, including standards for assessment and management of environmental and social risks and impacts, labor and working conditions, biodiversity conservation, indigenous peoples, resource efficiency and pollution prevention, community health, safety, and security, land acquisition and involuntary resettlement, and cultural heritage. \n', 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration."], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-2', '1-1']}, {'section': 'Ethics and Social Responsibility', 'code': ' E.8', 'question': 'Does the Board consider not only the financial performance but also the impact of the companyâ€™s operations on society and the environment?', 'answer': "Yes, the Board considers not only the financial performance but also the impact of the company's operations on society and the environment. The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects, including requirements for environmental and social risk and impact assessments, fair and safe working conditions, resource efficiency and pollution prevention, community health, safety, and security, land acquisition and involuntary resettlement, biodiversity conservation and sustainable management of living natural resources, engagement with indigenous peoples in a culturally appropriate manner, and identification and safeguarding of cultural heritage resources. \n", 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.'], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-1', '1-2', '1-3']}, {'section': 'Ethics and Social Responsibility', 'code': ' E.9', 'question': 'Does the Board monitor and report activities leading to good corporate citizenship and sustainability to demonstrate they are well coordinated?', 'answer': 'The provided document excerpts do not provide any information about whether or not the Board monitors and reports activities leading to good corporate citizenship and sustainability to demonstrate they are well coordinated. \n', 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.'], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-1', '1-2', '1-3']}, {'section': '"Accountability', 'code': ' Risk Management and Internal Control"', 'question': 'F.1', 'answer': 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC) has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These standards cover assessment and management of environmental and social risks and impacts, labor and working conditions, resource efficiency and pollution prevention, community health, safety and security, land acquisition and involuntary resettlement, biodiversity conservation and sustainable management of living natural resources, indigenous peoples, and cultural heritage. \n', 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration."], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-2', '1-3', '1-1']}, {'section': '"Accountability', 'code': ' Risk Management and Internal Control"', 'question': 'F.2', 'answer': 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC) has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects, including requirements for fair and safe working conditions, conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, engagement with indigenous peoples, and fair treatment of affected communities during land acquisition and resettlement. These standards also require clients to identify and assess potential environmental and social risks and impacts, develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts, safeguard cultural heritage resources, adopt cleaner production processes and pollution prevention measures, and ensure community health, safety, and security. \n', 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration."], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-3', '1-2', '1-1']}, {'section': '"Accountability', 'code': ' Risk Management and Internal Control"', 'question': 'F.3', 'answer': 'The International Finance Corporation has eight Performance Standards for investment projects, including standards for assessment and management of environmental and social risks and impacts, labor and working conditions, biodiversity conservation and sustainable management of living natural resources, indigenous peoples, resource efficiency and pollution prevention, community health, safety, and security, land acquisition and involuntary resettlement, and cultural heritage. \n', 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration."], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-3', '1-2', '1-1']}, {'section': '"Accountability', 'code': ' Risk Management and Internal Control"', 'question': 'F.4', 'answer': 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC) has eight Performance Standards, including Performance Standard 1 for environmental and social risk management, Performance Standard 2 for fair and safe working conditions, Performance Standard 3 for resource efficiency and pollution prevention, Performance Standard 4 for community health, safety, and security, Performance Standard 5 for land acquisition and involuntary resettlement, Performance Standard 6 for biodiversity conservation and sustainable management of living natural resources, Performance Standard 7 for indigenous peoples, and Performance Standard 8 for cultural heritage. These standards aim to ensure responsible investment projects that minimize negative impacts on the environment and local communities while respecting their rights and cultures. \n', 'source_contents': ["Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.'], 'source_pages': ['1-1', '1-0', '1-2']}, {'section': '"Accountability', 'code': ' Risk Management and Internal Control"', 'question': 'F.5', 'answer': 'Performance Standard 8 of the International Finance Corporation requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.\n', 'source_contents': ['Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.'], 'source_pages': ['1-3']}, {'section': '"Accountability', 'code': ' Risk Management and Internal Control"', 'question': 'F.6', 'answer': 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC) has eight Performance Standards for environmental and social requirements for investment projects, including standards for assessing and managing environmental and social risks and impacts, labor and working conditions, resource efficiency and pollution prevention, community health, safety, and security, land acquisition and involuntary resettlement, biodiversity conservation and sustainable management of living natural resources, indigenous peoples, and cultural heritage. These standards require clients to identify and assess potential negative impacts of projects and develop management plans to avoid or mitigate these impacts, as well as engage with affected communities and obtain their consent for any project activities that may affect them. Clients must also ensure fair and safe working conditions, minimize environmental footprints, and provide adequate compensation and livelihood restoration during land acquisition and resettlement. \n', 'source_contents': ['Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration."], 'source_pages': ['1-3', '1-2', '1-0', '1-1']}, {'section': '"Accountability', 'code': ' Risk Management and Internal Control"', 'question': 'F.7', 'answer': 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC) has eight Performance Standards for investment projects, including standards for assessing and managing environmental and social risks and impacts, labor and working conditions, resource efficiency and pollution prevention, community health, safety and security, land acquisition and involuntary resettlement, biodiversity conservation and sustainable management of living natural resources, indigenous peoples, and cultural heritage.\n', 'source_contents': ['Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration."], 'source_pages': ['1-2', '1-3', '1-0', '1-1']}, {'section': '"Accountability', 'code': ' Risk Management and Internal Control"', 'question': 'F.8', 'answer': 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC) has eight Performance Standards, which include requirements for assessing and managing environmental and social risks, ensuring fair and safe labor conditions, minimizing environmental impact, ensuring community health and safety, safeguarding cultural heritage and biodiversity, and respecting the rights of indigenous peoples. Clients must engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans for cultural heritage resources, obtain free, prior, and informed consent from indigenous peoples for any project activities that may affect them, and ensure the fair treatment of affected communities during land acquisition and resettlement. \n', 'source_contents': ['Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration."], 'source_pages': ['1-3', '1-2', '1-0', '1-1']}, {'section': '"Accountability', 'code': ' Risk Management and Internal Control"', 'question': 'F.9', 'answer': 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC) has eight Performance Standards, including Performance Standard 6 for biodiversity conservation and sustainable management of living natural resources, Performance Standard 7 for recognizing the rights of indigenous peoples, and Performance Standard 8 for identifying and safeguarding cultural heritage resources. Other standards cover the assessment and management of environmental and social risks and impacts, labor and working conditions, resource efficiency and pollution prevention, community health, safety, and security, and land acquisition and involuntary resettlement.\n', 'source_contents': ['Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration."], 'source_pages': ['1-3', '1-2', '1-0', '1-1']}, {'section': '"Accountability', 'code': ' Risk Management and Internal Control"', 'question': 'F.10', 'answer': 'Performance Standard 8 of the International Finance Corporation requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project and engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.\n', 'source_contents': ['Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.'], 'source_pages': ['1-3']}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.1', 'question': 'Does the company have policies and processes to ensure timely and balanced disclosure of all material information as required by all laws', 'answer': 'The provided document excerpts do not provide sufficient information to answer this question. \n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.2', 'question': 'Does the Annual Report cover', 'answer': "The document excerpts describe the International Finance Corporation's eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. The document does not mention an Annual Report or whether it covers any specific topic. \n", 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration."], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-3', '1-2', '1-1']}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.3', 'question': 'Does the Annual Report cover', 'answer': "The document provides information on the International Finance Corporation's eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects, including standards for cultural heritage, biodiversity conservation, indigenous peoples, resource efficiency, community health and safety, and land acquisition and resettlement. It is unclear if the document is an Annual Report or not. \n", 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration."], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-3', '1-2', '1-1']}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.4', 'question': 'Does the Annual Report cover', 'answer': "The excerpts provide information on the International Finance Corporation's eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects, including assessment and management of environmental and social risks and impacts, labor and working conditions, cultural heritage, biodiversity conservation and sustainable management of living natural resources, indigenous peoples, resource efficiency and pollution prevention, community health, safety, and security, and land acquisition and involuntary resettlement. There is no information provided on whether or not the Annual Report covers these standards. \n", 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration."], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-3', '1-2', '1-1']}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.5', 'question': 'As a minimum', 'answer': 'As a minimum, the International Finance Corporation (IFC) requires its clients to comply with eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These standards include assessing and managing environmental and social risks, ensuring fair and safe working conditions, conserving biodiversity and natural resources, recognizing the rights of indigenous peoples, identifying and safeguarding cultural heritage resources, ensuring community health, safety, and security, and establishing fair treatment of affected communities during land acquisition and resettlement. \n', 'source_contents': ['Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.'], 'source_pages': ['1-3', '1-1', '1-0', '1-2']}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.6', 'question': 'Does the Board disclose the management discussion and analysis as required in 7.1.1?', 'answer': 'The provided document excerpts do not provide information on whether or not the Board discloses the management discussion and analysis as required in 7.1.1. \n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.7', 'question': 'Has the Board provided disclosures as required in 7.1.1 on compliance with laws', 'answer': 'The provided document excerpts do not contain information relevant to whether the Board has provided disclosures as required in 7.1.1 on compliance with laws. \n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.8', 'question': 'Has the Board made all required disclosures', 'answer': "The provided document includes information about the International Finance Corporation (IFC)'s eight Performance Standards which define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects, including requirements for environmental and social risk assessments, labor and working conditions, cultural heritage, resource efficiency, community health and safety, land acquisition and involuntary resettlement, biodiversity conservation, and indigenous peoples. However, it does not provide information on whether the Board has made all required disclosures. \n", 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', 'Performance Standard 8: Cultural Heritage\nThis standard requires clients to identify and safeguard cultural heritage resources that may be affected by the project, and to engage with affected communities to develop appropriate management plans.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.'], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-3', '1-1', '1-2']}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.9', 'question': "Has the Board disclosed the company's risk management policy", 'answer': "The document provides information on the International Finance Corporation's (IFC) eight Performance Standards, which include requirements for environmental and social risk management, labor and working conditions, cultural heritage preservation, resource efficiency, community health and safety, land acquisition and resettlement, biodiversity conservation, and indigenous people's rights. However, there is no mention of whether or not the Board has disclosed the company's risk management policy specifically. \n", 'source_contents': ['The International Finance Corporation (IFC), a member of the World Bank Group, has eight Performance Standards that define its environmental and social requirements for investment projects. These Performance Standards are:\n\nPerformance Standard 1: Assessment and Management of Environmental and Social Risks and Impacts\nThis standard requires clients to identify and assess the potential environmental and social risks and impacts of their projects and develop a management plan to avoid or mitigate negative impacts.\n\nPerformance Standard 2: Labor and Working Conditions\nThis standard sets out requirements for fair and safe working conditions, including freedom of association and collective bargaining, non-discrimination, and no child labor or forced labor.', "Performance Standard 3: Resource Efficiency and Pollution Prevention\nThis standard aims to minimize the project's environmental footprint and maximize resource efficiency through the adoption of cleaner production processes, waste management, and pollution prevention measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 4: Community Health, Safety, and Security\nThis standard requires clients to ensure the safety and security of local communities and employees, including emergency preparedness and response measures.\n\nPerformance Standard 5: Land Acquisition and Involuntary Resettlement\nThis standard establishes requirements for the fair treatment of affected communities during the acquisition of land and resettlement of people, including adequate compensation and livelihood restoration.", 'Performance Standard 6: Biodiversity Conservation and Sustainable Management of Living Natural Resources\nThis standard aims to ensure the conservation of natural habitats and biodiversity, as well as the sustainable management of living natural resources, including fisheries and forests.\n\nPerformance Standard 7: Indigenous Peoples\nThis standard recognizes the rights of indigenous peoples and requires clients to engage with them in a culturally appropriate manner and obtain their free, prior, and informed consent for any project activities that may affect them.'], 'source_pages': ['1-0', '1-1', '1-2']}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.10', 'question': 'Has the Board disclosed information on shareholders', 'answer': 'No information is provided on whether the Board has disclosed information on shareholders.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.11', 'question': 'Has the Board disclosed all related-party transactions?', 'answer': 'There is no information provided about whether or not the Board has disclosed all related-party transactions.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}, {'section': 'Transparency and Disclosure', 'code': ' G.12', 'question': 'Does the Board include in its Annual Report a statement of policy on good governance and the status of the application of this Code?', 'answer': 'No information is provided about whether the Board includes in its Annual Report a statement of policy on good governance and the status of the application of this Code.\n', 'source_contents': [], 'source_pages': []}]